# **Mohammad Bin Shahed**

## Front-end development

+88 01624028821



Alif Housing, Adabor, Dhaka-1207



mdbinshahed5@gmail.com

binshahed-portfolio.vercel.app



github.com/binshahed



linkedin.com/in/binshahed

## **SUMMARY**

Experienced Frontend Developer with over 2 years of experience in React.js. Now, I'm curious about the magic happening behind the scenes in backend development. I have a knack for creating user-friendly interfaces and I'm excited to dive into full-stack projects. I love learning new things quickly and solving challenges. Ready to broaden my skills and contribute to the entire web development journey.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### E-Medical Solution Ltd.

Front End Developer

November 2022 – present Road No: 1, Shyamoli, Dhaka.

- Developing multiple complex UI systems in ERP projects. With a focus on complexity, I engineer solutions that seamlessly integrate into the ERP environment, enhancing user experiences.
- Collaborated with a team, gaining valuable teamwork experience.

#### Strativ.

### Junior Software Engineer

April 2022 – October 2022 Mirpur DOHS, Dhaka.

- Developed high-performance, multilanguage web applications, including a Lab System application, Booking System, and various feature enhancements in the vaccination system. Utilized ReactJS, React Router, Zustand, React Query, Ant Design, and Styled Components.
- Created web frontends for medical operations, aligning with client requirements and business architecture, while also ensuring the maintenance of current requirements in existing projects.
- Collaborated with different development and QA teams to code HTML/CSS mockups, test, and validate projects throughout the development process.

### **Kendrik Studio.**

#### Web Developer Intern

January 2022 – March 2022 Gulsan-2, Dhaka.



Assisted the development team and maintaining 3 websites.

## SKILL

Javascript, React.js, Next.js, Redux, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, MUI, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Ant Design, il8next, React query, Zustand, firebase, TypeScript, C, UI/UX.

# **EDUCATION**

### Dhaka International University.

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering. (2019-2023) Institute Of Computer Science and Technology Feni.

Diploma in Computer Technology. (2013-2017)

# **STRENGTHS**

## Proficient in UI/UX design

Recognized for intuitive UI/UX design prowess.

#### **Communication Skills**

Known for excellent communication.

#### **Team Player**

Valued for collaborative spirit and cooperative approach to achieving team goals.

> **Mohammad Bin Shahed** Date: 17 April 2024